adoreme.com 2016-10-08

# Privacy Policy

**Last Updated: September 8, 2016**

  **INTRODUCTION**

Adore Me, Inc. (“Adore Me”, “we”, or “us) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, protect, use and share information about you when you use Adore Me website located at adoreme.com (the “Site”), the Adore Me mobile app (the “App”), the Adore Me mobile site (the “Mobile Site”) and related services (together with the Site, the App, the Mobile Site, and the Adore Me Content, as defined below, the “Services”).

 We hope this information increases your confidence in Adore Me and enhances your experience with Adore Me. Each time that you use the Services, you signify that you agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy you must discontinue using the Website and the Services.

This Privacy Policy addresses the following topics:

  1. Information/Data We Collect and How We Use It
  2. Disclosure of Passive or User-Submitted Data
  3. Communication from Us or from the Website
  4. Choice/Opt-Out/Unsubscribe
  5. Offline Collection, Use & Disclosure of Information
  6. Security of your Account
  7. Changes in Ownership
  8. Use of our Services by Children
  9. Special Notice for California Residents
  10. Contact Us/Feedback
  11. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We collect two types of data about individuals: (1) technical data which is automatically collected from all visitors to the Website and from all individuals that use the Services (“Passive Data Collection”) and (2) information that you or others voluntarily submit to us (“User-Submitted Information”). 

“Personal Information,” as that term is used in this Privacy Policy, is information that allows the direct identification of an individual, such as a name or email address, and information that is directly combined with such identifying information. Our primary purpose in collecting Personal Information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We only collect Personal Information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

**Passive Data Collection**

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on and use of the Website. We use this information to do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community.  This information allows us to, among other things, help make Services easier for you to use, help you quickly find information, products, and services, help us create content on this Services that is most relevant to you, and alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer.

_**Mobile Device Information**_

 When you download or use our Adore Me mobile application (“App”), we receive information about your mobile device (but not the native manufacturer unique identifier for your device) for purpose of tracking unique downloads. We register your device, and may use the identifier to send you push notifications about your transactions with our service.

_**Log Files**_

 Like most websites, we automatically receive and record certain information about our users’ behavior on our Website and when using our Services. Our servers automatically gather technical information about our Website traffic and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We aggregate this information with other pieces of information to analyze trends, to administer and improve the Services, to track users’ movements around the Website and to make inventory purchasing decisions that will best serve our customer base. Pages of the Website may also use devices that permit us to count users who have visited those pages and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

If we directly combine any information gathered through passive means with Personal Information, we treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. Otherwise, we use information collected by passive means in aggregated forms.

_**Cookies and Clear GIFs**_

 A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping or tracking purposes. A cookie (sometimes referred to as local storage object or LSO) is a data file placed on a device.  Cookies can be created through a variety of web-related protocols and technologies, such as HTTP (sometimes referred to as “browser cookies”), and HTML5. We use cookies and other tracking technologies on the Website and Services. Cookies help us enhance your experience by speeding your navigation through the Services, recognizing you, and tracking your usage of the Website and the Services. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Adore Me only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or other third-parties.

Cookies are necessary to use certain portions of our Services.  You can remove certain cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" menu. You may also configure your browser to prevent cookies from being set on your computer; however, if you reject cookies your ability to use the Website and Services may be limited and you may not be able to use certain features of the Website.  In particular, cookies are necessary to select and purchase products.

We also employ a software technology called clear gifs, also referred to as action tags, that help manage content on the Website by tracking what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice / Opt-out” section of this Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Advertisers**

 We may from time to time use third party advertising companies to help us further enhance our users’ experience and to better tailor our content to our individual customers.  Third party advertising companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this Website and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. These third party cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and is not linked to any personal information collected by us.

**User-Submitted Information**

_**Registration**_

In order to use the Website and the Services, you must first register with us and create a user name and password. We use this information to contact you about the products and Services on our Website in which you have expressed interest.

In order to better tailor our Services to you, we may also ask for your personal characteristics, such as cup size, band size, and dress size.

_  **Orders**_

If you order a product from us, we request certain Personal Information from you on our order form, whether you access the Services from our App or the Website. You must provide accurate contact information (including name, shipping address, telephone number) and financial information (including credit card number and expiration date). Further, when you order Adore Me gift card, we may require that you provide the recipient’s name, shipping address and email address.

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

_**Surveys or Contests**_

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys or contests on our site. If you participate, we will request certain Personal Information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information.

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor Website traffic, or to personalize the Website (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys) and to send participants an email newsletter. By participating in a survey or contest you submit to that activity’s terms and conditions, including providing us with permission, if required, to share your Personal Information with sponsors of that survey and/or contest. 

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests, in which case the third party's service providers use of our users’ Personal Information will be governed by its privacy policy, which will be made available to users at the time they enroll for the survey or contest.

_**Refer-A-Friend**_

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Services, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Website. Adore Me stores your friend’s name and email address for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.  We will make clear that our email to your friend was sent at your request.  You should check that your friends consent to your sharing of their personal information before submitting it to us. 

We will, at your request, send a follow up email to your friend if we have not heard from her/him within three days.  If your friend does not wish to receive future invitations or emails from us, your friend may contact us our Customer Care department at [Claims@adoreme.com](mailto:Claims@adoreme.com) at 1.800.433.2367 (Monday – Sunday 8:30 a.m. – 8:30 p.m. (EST)) to request that we remove her/his email address from our mailing list.

  _ **T** **hird-Party Account Credentials**_

When you provide us with your third party account credentials, to such services as Facebook and Twitter, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts may be transmitted into your account with us. However, information transmitted to our Website from your third party account will be covered by this Privacy Policy.

_**Chat Rooms/ Discussion Boards**_

If you choose to post messages in our chat rooms or other public message areas or leave feedback for other users, please note that such information is available to anyone with Internet access. We may, but are not obligated to, collect the information you post in our chat rooms or other public message areas to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law. PLEASE BE CAREFUL WHEN DISCLOSING ANY INFORMATION IN CHAT ROOMS, DISCUSSION BOARDS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE INFORMATION YOU PUBLICLY DISCLOSE. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these Services in a manner that is inconsistent with the [Terms and Conditions](https://www.adoreme.com/terms-conditions).

 2\. DISCLOSURE OF PASSIVE OR USER-SUBMITTED DATA

_**Adore Me Partners**_

Adore Me engages in marketing and promotional activities with carefully screened brands, or, “Partners,” which we think will appeal to our user base. We may make our user list available to Partners so that you may receive catalogs, product information, or promotions from our Partners. If you prefer we don’t use your information for partner promotions, please email our Customer Care team at [Help@AdoreMe.com](mailto:help@adoreme.com) or write to us at Adore Me, Inc., ,205 W. 39th Street, 16th Floor, New York, New York 10018. 

From time to time, Partners may also be provided with non- identifying or aggregate information indicating the demographic information of users on our Website, buying behavior, and opportunities to market to select segments of our customer base indirectly. When we share aggregate user data, we do so in a way that it cannot be linked with a user's Personal Information.

_**Service Providers**_

We may provide Personal Information to third parties for their use in performing internal business functions (e.g., mailing, maintenance, security, data analytics, email transmission, CRM, database management services, credit card payment processing or data hosting), or for performing client-facing services (e.g. delivery partners such as the U.S. Postal Service, United Parcel Service, and Federal Express) on our behalf. These service providers agree to only use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and for no other purpose than to provide us or our Partners with the contracted-for services.

_**Related Parties**_

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our affiliates (including a parent company, subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us), in which case we will seek to require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

_**Address Verification**_

We use third party software to verify your identity and address, in order to ensure proper shipping and billing procedures for your purchases.  The third party software provider will only use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and for no other purpose than to provide us the with contracted-for services.

_**As required by Law / Certain Business Transactions**_

We may disclose Personal Information if we have a good-faith belief that doing so is required by a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order or otherwise required by law or in connection with an actual or proposed corporate transaction, investigation, or insolvency proceeding involving all or part of the business or asset to which the information pertains. This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of the United States, where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction.

_**To Protect Rights**_

Additionally, we may disclose Personal Information where we, in good faith, deem it appropriate or necessary to prevent violation of the Terms and Conditions or our other agreements; take precautions against liability; protect the rights, property, or safety of Adore Me, any individual, or the general public; maintain and protect the security and integrity of our Services or infrastructure; protect ourselves and our Services from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; or assist government enforcement agencies.

_  **Co-branded Sites**_

In the event that that our Website links to other websites that include our branding, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those other websites. Visitors to those websites are advised to carefully read the privacy policies and terms and conditions on those individual websites.

_**Tracking Technologies and Tailored Advertisements / Choices**_

Adore Me also partners with advertising companies to place our advertising on publisher websites on the Internet. These advertising companies collect anonymous information about your visits to our Website by placing and reading cookies on the device you use to access our web site. The cookies do not collect or use Personal Information. Like the cookies we place and read directly, these tracking technologies are used to analyze user behaviors in the aggregate. They are used to analyze and optimize our App or Website, measure conversion, and tailor content to interests.

 California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how we respond to “Do Not Track” browser settings. Our Website is not at this time configured to read or respond to “do not track” settings or signals in your browser headings, which vary by browser provider, because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed.  We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created. In lieu of a browser-based opt-out solution, you can utilize the Network Advertising Initiative approved methods for placement of “opt-out” cookies described [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). Our Website and those of our third party advertisers or other vendors are configured to read and honor these opt-out cookies, so long as they are present on your computer. (If you delete all cookies, you will need to reset your opt-out cookies.) Specific instructions on how to do so are available here. However, please be aware that we do not control these opt-out processes.

_**Links to Other Websites**_

The Website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Adore Me. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Adore Me and we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every website.

  **Retaining Your Data**

 We will retain both passively-collected and user-submitted data as necessary for legitimate business purposes and to the extent required by law, even if you disable your account.  Please feel free to contact our Legal Department at [legal@adoreme.com](mailto:legal@adoreme.com) if you have any questions about this policy. 

 3\. COMMUNICATION FROM US OR THE WEBSITE

We use your contact information to communicate with you about Adore Me and our marketing partners, as described below.

_  **Special Offers and Updates**_

We will occasionally send you information on Services, products, special deals, and promotions. You can take advantage of promotions by entering the promotion code provided at the time of checkout. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the “Choice / Opt-out” section of this Privacy Policy.

We send newsletters, usually by email. Please see the “Choice / Opt-out” section of this Privacy Policy to discontinue newsletters.

_**Messages about the Service and Your Account**_

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our Services are temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

Based upon the Personal Information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, to manage your account, and to provide the best customer service possible.

_**SMS Notifications**_

We may occasionally send you information on about your account or our Services via text message.  Please note that your carrier’s standard charges, data rates and other fees may apply.  If you do not wish to receive SMS text messages from us, please adjust your preferences on our Website under “My Account,” “Notifications,” or contact Customer Care at 1.800.433.2367 (Monday – Sunday 8:30 a.m. – 8:30 p.m. (EST)) or by email at [Claims@AdoreMe.com](mailto:Claims@AdoreMe.com).

_**App Notifications**_

If you download and use our App, and have enabled push notifications on your mobile device, we may send you alerts and notifications through push notifications, for example, to communicate shipping status for goods you purchased. You can opt out of these messages by changing the settings on your mobile device.

 4\. CHOICE/OPT-OUT OF/UNSUBSCRIBE FROM COMMUNICATION

If you wish to reduce the frequency or alter the type of communication you receive you may change your contact preferences at the “Notifications” tab of Your Account on [www.adoreme.com](http://www.adoreme.com/) at any time.  If your information changes, if you wish you unsubscribe from all communications from us, or if you require further assistance, please contact us by telephone at 1.800.433.2367 Monday – Sunday 8:30 a.m. – 8:30 p.m. (EST) or by email to our Customer Care department at [Help@AdoreMe.com](mailto:help@adoreme.com) and our agents will assist you to change your account settings and/or deactivate your account.  Please do not email your credit card number or other sensitive information to this email address.

 5\. OFFLINE COLLECTION, USE & DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

As you might expect, the majority of information Adore Me collects is obtained through our Website and the use of our Services.  However, we also take steps to protect information we collection “offline.”  We will treat all Private Information received, including fax, phone calls, and letters, consistently with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

 6\. SECURITY OF YOUR ACCOUNT

The security of your information is important to us, including, but not limited to, the Personal Information collected via the Website. We use reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, unauthorized access, misuse, alteration and destruction of Personal Information under our control, both during the transmission and once we receive it. This includes, but is not limited to, the use of firewalls and encryption. Our Website incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") protection for all financial transactions conducted through our Website, our App and our Mobile Site.  We also take several steps to protect the physical storage of your personal information in our facilities, including the storage of servers in a secure physical environment, behind a locked cage and an electronic firewall.

 It is your responsibility to make sure that your personal information is accurate and that your password(s) and account registration information are secure and not shared with third-parties.

 Although we make good faith efforts to maintain the security of such Personal Information, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and we cannot guarantee that it will remain free from unauthorized access, use, disclosure, or alteration. Further, while we work hard to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent “hackers” or other unauthorized persons from illegally accessing or obtaining this information. To minimize the risk to you, we keep Personal Information no longer than necessary for legitimate business purpose or as required by law.

As part of securing personal data stored on our servers, we restrict access to Personal Information to Adore Me employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve the Services. These individuals are bound by strict confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

If we learn of a security breach, we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Services or the Website or by providing Personal Information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Services.

If a security systems breach occurs, we may post a notice on our homepage ([www.adoreme.com](http://www.adoreme.com/)) or elsewhere on the Website and may send email to you at the email address you have provided to us. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. This notice paragraph applies to users of Services and the Website.

7\. CHANGES OF OWNERSHIP

In the event of a change in ownership, or a merger with, acquisition by, or transfer or sale of all or a portion of our assets to, another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of your Personal Information, including email addresses, to that entity.

 8\. CHILDREN

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) protects the online privacy of children under 13 years of age. Adore Me and the Website are not directed toward individuals under the age of eighteen (18), and we request that such individuals do not provide Personal Information through our Website. Additionally, we do not knowingly collect or maintain Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18, unless or except as permitted by law. If we learn that Personal Information has been collected from a user under 18 years of age on or through the Website, then we will take the appropriate steps to cause this information to be deleted. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 18 who has registered on the Website or you believe has otherwise provided Personal Information to Adore Me, please contact Adore Me at [legal@adoreme.com](mailto:legal@adoreme.com) to have that child’s account terminated and information deleted.

 9\. NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

If you are a resident of the state of California, California’s “Shine the Light” law permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your Personal Information by us to a third party for the third party's direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [legal@adoreme.com](mailto:legal@adoreme.com) or write us at: Adore Me, Inc. 205 W. 39th Street, 16th Floor, New York, New York 10018, Attention: Legal Department.

 10\. CONTACT US/FEEDBACK

If you have questions, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [legal@adoreme.com](mailto:legal@adoreme.com) or Adore Me, Inc. 205 W. 39th Street, 16th Floor, New York, New York 10018, Attention: Legal Department.

 11\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Website, with the "Effective Date" posted at the top of the Privacy Policy. We may revise and update this Privacy Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy or how we handle your personal information, or we are going to use any Personal Information in a manner that is materially different from that stated in our Privacy Policy at the time we collected such information, we will give you reasonable and appropriate notice regarding the change. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on the Website. You should check the Website frequently for updates.  By using our Website or Services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current Privacy Policy.
